{
  "card_id": "mr-beat-2026",
  "user_handle": "MrBeat",
  "answer_id": "stEdsC2hty",
  "status": "active",
  "win_probability": 0.5,
  "target_win_prob": 0.5,
  "purchase_price": 1,
  "purchase_prob": 0.5,
  "created_time": 1768964370819,
  "grid": [
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Stagflation",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "96LyEIygOO",
      "answer_text": "Stagflation"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "War with Venezuela",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "ANpqOnqAcL",
      "answer_text": "War with Venezuela"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "AI bubble pops (but it's not that bad)",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "LSL8luzQQR",
      "answer_text": "AI bubble pops (but it's not that bad)"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Blue wave midterms",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "dz8tIcnAz5",
      "answer_text": "Blue wave midterms"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "AI slop completely takes over platforms",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "Sy8dqLCS2l",
      "answer_text": "AI slop completely takes over platforms"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Everyone becomes a hipster",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "Og9AP092up",
      "answer_text": "Everyone becomes a hipster"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "A major merger of streaming services",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "LzdlzclRR0",
      "answer_text": "A major merger of streaming services"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Solar power doubles",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "U8cpdNyuds",
      "answer_text": "Solar power doubles"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Chain movie theaters close across the country",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "s2PQAsqLyS",
      "answer_text": "Chain movie theaters close across the country"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Americans become more united",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "LytLnZZS9h",
      "answer_text": "Americans become more united"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "More governments embrace Bitcoin",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "u9ICqz8pEZ",
      "answer_text": "More governments embrace Bitcoin"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Trump has (another?) stroke",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "E0pQEIS95l",
      "answer_text": "Trump has (another?) stroke"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "FREE SPACE",
      "prob": 1.0,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": null,
      "answer_text": "FREE SPACE"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Gen Alpha rebels against digital media",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "ZPSlQhgyLU",
      "answer_text": "Gen Alpha rebels against digital media"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Really bad hurricane season",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "zyIZ2tLOhE",
      "answer_text": "Really bad hurricane season"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Measles cases triple",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "nE6lg8IIAA",
      "answer_text": "Measles cases triple"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Emo makes a comeback",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "tpLz5tISc5",
      "answer_text": "Emo makes a comeback"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "EV sales skyrocket",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "zQNlQh2Ztn",
      "answer_text": "EV sales skyrocket"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "A new nonpartisan political movement starts",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "q25UZEPsds",
      "answer_text": "A new nonpartisan political movement starts"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "YouTube surpasses Netflix in paid subscribers",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "R8lCctICSp",
      "answer_text": "YouTube surpasses Netflix in paid subscribers"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Twitter shuts down",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "gL5Q2hOh5n",
      "answer_text": "Twitter shuts down"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "More assassinations",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "LzUpd5nygE",
      "answer_text": "More assassinations"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Obesity rates dramatically decline",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "0n0PtgRgh9",
      "answer_text": "Obesity rates dramatically decline"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Cyber terrorism incident",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "PQQlN6s90t",
      "answer_text": "Cyber terrorism incident"
    },
    {
      "slug": "mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "question": "Robot restaurant trend",
      "prob": 0.5,
      "resolved": null,
      "url": "https://manifold.markets/Evansbot/mr-beats-2026-bingo-card",
      "answer_id": "98ptquIpAp",
      "answer_text": "Robot restaurant trend"
    }
  ],
  "card_type": "featured",
  "external_link": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0DHSnDvyuJI",
  "external_link_label": "Watch Video"
}